hitsfilm.com 2015-04-09

# Privacy Policy - HITS

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you about the types of information gathered by VHX Corporation (“we”, “us”) when you use VHX, how we use and safeguard that information, and the degree to which you may control the collection and use of that information.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you are a registered VHX user, we will attempt to inform you of any material changes by email. Otherwise, you may view the most recent Privacy Policy on the VHX website. Your continued use of VHX constitutes your agreement with the existing and updated policies.

### Information Collection and Use

We will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. You may elect not to provide any or all such information, but if so you may not be able to use all features of VHX.

As part of the registration process, we will ask you to provide information such as your name and email address in order to create your VHX account. If you choose to offer a program for sale or rental on VHX, we will ask you to provide your Dwolla, bank account or Paypal account information so we may compensate you for those sales and rentals. If you choose to buy or rent (“Purchase”) a program, we will ask you to provide information regarding your payment service of choice (e.g. credit card, PayPal, Google Checkout) so we may facilitate your Purchase.

VHX does not collect or store any personal financial information in connection with purchases. While we do offer you the option to store your credit or debit card payment information to make future purchases easier, we do not store the actual card number or related personal financial information. Rather, that information is provided to a third party for secure storage, and we use a secure “token” associated with that information to facilitate your purchase. These tokens do not include personal financial information. All personal financial information required to complete your purchase will be securely collected and provided to a third party vendor who will process payments and complete transactions.

### Analytics

We may automatically collect and store certain information about your interaction with the VHX website, including IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, solely to improve the quality of our products and services. We also use cookies to make it easier for you to use VHX. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our services.

### Email Notices

When you register with VHX, we will send you a welcome email that includes information about VHX and your account. If you make a Purchase, we will send you an email with information about your Purchase. You may also request to receive periodic emails from us notifying you about new or upcoming VHX products or services. If you later decide you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt-out as instructed in each email. Be advised, however, that you may not opt-out of receiving emails from us related to your purchases, technical support requests, or updates to the VHX Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.

If you forget your account login information, you may request that we send it to the email address associated with your account. Please take steps to keep your account information secure to prevent unauthorized access.

### Disclosure

We understand how highly our users value the privacy and security of their personally identifiable information. We will disclose information collected from and about you only as follows: (1) to Producers, as detailed below; (2) to our related companies, service providers and suppliers, to enable them to fulfill a product or service request or to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Service or of our rights or the rights of any third party; and (4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.

### Disclosure to Producers

If you choose to make a Purchase, the Producer (as defined in our Terms of Service) will receive your email address as well as certain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., date and time of purchase, geographic location). The Producer may choose to send you emails regarding your Purchase as well as the Producer’s other products and services. VHX has no control over a Producer’s activities with respect to communications with purchasers.

We do not disclose any of your personal financial information to Producers.

### Business Transitions

In the event VHX Corporation goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, any personally identifiable information we have on record will likely be among the assets transferred. The transferred information will remain subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any subsequent updated versions.

### Information Security

We employ encryption and other security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We take commercially reasonable steps to protect this information by using secure-socket-layer (“SSL”) to protect the transmission of such information. However, please be advised that while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized access from occurring. Please take steps to maintain the security of your account information.

### Children

Use of VHX is restricted to individuals 13 years old or older. We therefore will not knowingly collect, store, use, or disclose any information regarding children under the age of 13. We will only knowingly collect, store, and use information regarding children older than 13 but younger than 18 with the consent of the child’s parent or guardian. If we are informed that we have unknowingly collected information in contravention of these policies, we will immediately delete that information from our systems.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or any VHX product or service, please don’t hesitate to [contact us](http://vhx.tv/contact).

Effective Date: 20 November 2014.
